uxbooth.com 2010-06-14

# Privacy Policy | UX Booth

The privacy of our visitors at UXBooth.com is important to us.

At UXBooth.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit UXBooth.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.  
Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This may allow us to keep you logged into special site features such as our Forums, or automatically fill in data for you in various forms.

We also use third party advertisements on UXBooth.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that UXBooth.com is not responsible for the privacy practices, or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

### Latest Resources

  * #### [Process: Early user research, simulation and evaluation](http://www.uxbooth.com/resources/process-early-user-research-simulation-and-evaluation/)

“And if you don’t do this in an early stage, in a majority of the cases it simply is not possible to change it in a later stage. (…

  * #### [Use Shadowbox to show information without losing your customers attention](http://www.uxbooth.com/resources/use-shadowbox-to-show-information-without-losing-your-customers-attention/)

I was reading an article by Erin Jo Richey over at uxbooth.com on cart abandonment and I wanted to implement some of the ideas into my magento…

  * #### [The Golden Rules of Usable Web Design](http://www.uxbooth.com/resources/the-golden-rules-of-usable-web-design/)

“The Golden Rules of Usable Web Design” by Theo Mandel, Ph.D. Presented in Denver, CO on May 19, 2010.

Submit a resource

### UX Booth Community
